This isn't a prison. It's a machine.
Escape Plan 2: Hades is a action, thriller, crime
film directed by Steven C. Miller.
Ray Breslin manages an elite team of security specialists trained in the art of
breaking people out of the world's most impenetrable prisons.
When his most trusted operative, Shu Ren, is kidnapped and disappears inside the most elaborate
prison ever built, Ray must track him down with the help of some of his former friends.
Ray Breslin, played by Sylvester Stallone.
Trent DeRosa, played by Dave Bautista.
Luke Walken, played by Jesse Metcalfe.
Hush, played by 50 Cent.
Shu Ren, played by Huang Xiaoming.
Jaspar Kimbral, played by Wes Chatham.
Escape Plan 2: Hades is a 2018 American direct-to-video
prison action thriller film directed by Steven C.
It is the sequel to the 2013 film Escape Plan, and the second
installment in the Escape Plan film series.
It stars Sylvester Stallone and Curtis Jackson reprising their roles from the first film, with Dave Bautista,
Huang Xiaoming, Jaime King, Jesse Metcalfe, Titus Welliver, and Wes Chatham joining the cast.
Escape Plan 2: Hades was released straight-to-DVD in the United States but received theatrical
releases in such countries as Russia on June 28, 2018, and in China on June 29, 2018.
The film received negative reviews from critics; it grossed $17.6 million in some theaters and
$4.2 million in domestic home market against a production budget of $20 million.
A sequel, Escape Plan: The Extractors, was released in 2019.
The film explores themes of sequel, high tech surveillance,
hacking, cousin relationship, held hostage.
The tone is mind_bending and thought_provoking and intense.